<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ChiSports Data</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ChiSports Data</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Seeing a New Reynaldo Lopez</title>
      <link>/2019/08/23/we-re-seeing-a-new-reynaldo-lopez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/08/23/we-re-seeing-a-new-reynaldo-lopez/</guid>
      <description>“Starting today you’re going to see a different pitcher going forward for the second half of the season.”
Those were the words Reynaldo Lopez expressed through an interpreter after getting shelled in a July 4th start against the Detroit Tigers. At the time, Lopez had the highest ERA (6.34) among qualified pitchers. Since then, though, Lopez has lived up to his word as we have seen a much better pitcher since the all-star break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a reset button: How Jim Boylen changed the 2019 Bulls</title>
      <link>/2019/01/24/looking-for-a-reset-button-how-jim-boylen-changed-the-2019-bulls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/24/looking-for-a-reset-button-how-jim-boylen-changed-the-2019-bulls/</guid>
      <description>Since taking over for Fred Hoiberg at the beginning of December, Jim Boylen has taken a ton of criticism for his approach as the new lead man for the Bulls, but rightfully so. His “play hard” mentality and push to be the best conditioned team in the league (defending push-up champs) hasn’t resonated with players of this era. Not only is this management style not fitting well, his philosophy as a coach doesn’t fit the mold of how the league has trended with a barrage of three point attempts coming per game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Joc Pederson</title>
      <link>/2019/01/21/evaluating-joc-pederson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/01/21/evaluating-joc-pederson/</guid>
      <description>With rumblings about a potential trade for Joc Pederson, the White Sox are continuing to remain active this offseason, although we are all waiting for that one BIG signing to occur still. If you’re active on Twitter, you’ll notice a lot of your favorite White Sox accounts would tell you that Pederson would have ranked 1st in almost every statistical category for the White Sox last season. Let’s take a look at some of the numbers and see if we can pinpoint what Joc Pederson brings to the table for the South Siders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example</title>
      <link>/2018/12/26/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/26/example/</guid>
      <description> EXAMPLE POST
Rose: &amp;quot;I’m happy I didn’t change throughout this whole process. I remained myself. I stayed true to my family. There was a lot of people that jumped off the boat when I was going through things. I seen who they were. I know what’s fake love and what’s real love.&amp;quot;
&amp;mdash; K.C. Johnson (@KCJHoop) December 27, 2018  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:05:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Why start a blog? As a Chicago kid growing up on the south side, I’ve learned to become passionate about our sports team as I’ve been cheering on the White Sox and Bulls for as long as I can remember (my football allegiance belongs to those cheeseheads to the north which can be discussed another day). In recent years, we’ve seen our favorite sports continue to evolve on the basis of data and analytics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2015/07/23/hello-r-markdown/</guid>
      <description>Example Markdown Let’s pretend this an example post types here, saved in RStudio and pushed to GitHub.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.:19.0 3rd Qu.: 56.00 ## Max. :25.0 Max. :120.00 fit &amp;lt;- lm(dist ~ speed, data = cars) fit ## ## Call: ## lm(formula = dist ~ speed, data = cars) ## ## Coefficients: ## (Intercept) speed ## -17.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>